CONTACT



647-401-8005



aarthomas01@gmail.com



Github.com/aa-thomas



A<u>aronthomas.dev</u>



Brampton, ON, Canada

EDUCATION

Juno College Institute of Technology - 2022

• Web Development Bootcamp

Team TreeHouse TechDegree - 2022

• Full-Stack JavaScript Program

General Education Diploma - 2017

CORE COMPETENCIES

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Node.js
- SQL
- Firebase
- Git
- Adaptability
- Complex problem-solving
- Communication
- Time Management
- Paired programming & teambased development

AARON THOMAS

FULL-STACK JAVASCRIPT WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a full-stack web developer with over one year of experience building both front-end and back-end projects with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js and SQL. I am currently looking to turn my passion and hobby into employment. I am an eager learner looking to join a team with solid mentorship, where I can develop my skills while also being able to contribute as much as possible.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

React Habit Tracker App

- An app that records number of times a user completes a habit, with realtime charts.
- · Built using React, Firebase, CSS
- Live website | Github

React Movie Gif Spoilers App

- An app where the user can search a movie and return 3 gifs that describe the plot.
- Built using React, Firebase, CSS, API's
- Live Website | Github

Worldly Recipes

- An app that returns recipes based on a users search
- · Built using HTML, CSS, Vanilla JS and API's
- Live Website | Github

PSD Design Conversion

- A mock website converted from a PSD design
- Built using HTML, CSS and Vanilla JS
- Live Website | Github

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pepsico Beverages Canada - Forklift Operator June 2017 - September 2022

- Responsible for managing workflows of personnel and materials during \$900,000 renovation.
- Contributed to 24.75% revenue increase from 2018 -2021 by using keen organizational and time management skills to reduce inefficiencies, leading to production of thousands of extra bottles per day.

Best Buy Inc. - Sales Associate

December 2013 - January 2016

- Identify customer needs quickly and turn into technology based solutions.
- Successfully diffused customer issues using patience and excellent listening skills.
- Able to suggestively sell/upsell products and services.

References available upon request